LoganAlleyne

Web Developer

Contact







About_

I'm a Web developer based in Brighton & Hove who is strives to create visually appealing, meaningful, and clean web experiences using modern technologies.

I'm passionate about user experience and always try to balance aesthetic appeal & flare with functionality, usability, and accessibility.

Education

Computing for Digital Media (BSc hons) University of Sussex

A three year course including modules: Web 3D Applications, Human-Computer Interaction, Technology Enhanced Learning, and Software Engineering.

BTEC Level 3 Extended Diploma IT A two year A-level equivalent IT course

Skills_

Front-End	Design	Workflow	Other
HTML	Illustrator	GitHub	PHP
CSS & SCSS	Indesign	Agile	Laravel
Tailwind	XD	Kanban	three.js
JavaScript	Photoshop		Vuex
Vue	User stories		Vite
			Netlify

Experience

Technical Production Manager BrandStencil | Hove | Feburary 2021 - Present

BrandStencil is a SaaS brand management tool largely based on templates, asset management, and other features allowing for the creation of dynamic and brand compliant materials, with the vast majority of clients being in the charity sector. My first role was Template developer where I would build pixel perfect dynamic templates based on designs provided to us by clients using HTML, SCSS, Laravel, and BrandStencil's own framework.

Over time my responsibilities grew to include among other things, creating and improving production processes & workflows, interviewing and then managing freelance developers, helping develop new features for the platform, and taking over all front-end development for the application.

Technology: HTML, SCSS, Tailwind, PHP, Laravel, Blade, JavaScript Vue, Vuex, REST APIs, XPath, XML, JSON, YAML, Docker, MySQL

Junior Product Developer ReedPop | Brighton | July 2020 - December 2020

Working a Junior Front-end web developer I maintained and updated an array of different sites, including Eurogamer.net and RockPaperShotgun.com. I also helped to build all new digital events sites for very large digital only events such as PAX x EGX for which we had over 12 million impressions.

Technology: Django, Python, Wordpress, PHP, Docker

Technical Operator The Edit_ | Brighton | September 2019 - July 2020

Working in television post-production, helping with assistant editing and technical support, with a broad number of responsibilities and a variety of challenges daily in a high pressure environment as part of a small highly collaborative team.

Technology: Avid Media Composer & NEXIS, PC Hardware, Networking